=My Little Perfection= (Adapted from the novel 'Difficult Pregnancy')
= حبيبتي الصغيرة = (مكيفة من 'الحمل الصعب' الجديد)
=Episode 2=
= الحلقة 2 =
The doctor said
قال الطبيب
both of you have to take this medicine.
كلاكما يجب أن يتناولا هذا الدواء
Why did you vomit it?
لماذا تقيأت عليه؟
This medicine is quite expensive.
هذا الدواء باهظ الثمن
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
The doctor said this medicine has to be finished.
قال الطبيب إن هذا الدواء يجب الانتهاء منه
Mom.
أمي
Go to the hospital with us.
اذهبي معنا إلى المستشفى
We're really worried about you.
نحن قلقون عليك حقا
Understood, Mom.
فهمت يا أمي
Give it to me.
أعطيه إلي
As long as I finish all the medicine,
طالما أنني أنتهي من كل الدواء
you'll go to the hospital, right?
سوف تذهب إلى المستشفى، أليس كذلك؟
What?
ماذا؟
We've finished the medicine.
لقد أنهينا الدواء
You have to go to the hospital.
يجب أن تذهب إلى المستشفى
Don't pour it away.
لا تسكبها
You haven't even gotten pregnant yet.
لم تتحن بعد حتى
Darling.
دارلينغ
What's wrong?
ما الخطب؟
No way.
لا يمكن
We must take her to the hospital.
يجب أن نأخذها إلى المستشفى
Mom!
أمي!
- What? - Listen to me.
- ماذا - استمعوا إلي
Listen to me.
استمعوا إلي
Mom.
أمي
- I'm not going! - Go to the hospital.
- لن أذهب يا أمي - اذهبي إلى المشفى
Put me down!
أنزلني
- You must go. - Mom!
- يجب أن تذهبي - أمي - أمي!
- Put me down! - Listen to me.
- أنزلني! - أمسكوا بي - اسمعني
- Mom. - Don't come here.
- أمي - لا تأت إلى هنا
Calm down.
اهدأ
Mom.
أمي
- Go to the hospital! - You promised.
- اذهبي إلى المستشفى! - لقد وعدتني - وعدتني -
You promised to let me have a grandchild.
وعدت أن تدعني أنجب حفيدًا
Now you're forcing me to go to the hospital.
تجبرتني على الذهاب إلى المشفى الآن
You must go to the hospital today.
يجب أن تذهب إلى المشفى اليوم
If I don't have a grandchild,
إن لم يكن لديّ جدة
what's the point of living?
ما الهدف من العيش؟
- Wait! - Mom!
- انتظري - أمي
What should we do now?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل الآن؟
We can't let her have her way anymore.
لا يمكننا أن ندعها وشأنها بعد الآن
I know.
أعرف
I'm also confused right now.
أنا في حيرة من أمري حاليًا
Have you slept?
هل نمت؟
Yes, I have.
نعم لقد فعلت
I prepared some milk for you to drink before bed.
حضّرت لك بعض الحليب قبل السرير
Here, drink it.
هيا، اشربيه
It'll make the baby fair and chubby.
سوف يجعل الطفل عادل وسباقا
Mom.
أمي
I've already brushed my teeth.
لقد أنظف أسناني بالفعل
I'll drink it.
سأشربها
No, Jiahui.
لا يا جياهوي
This is for you.
هذه لك
Come on, drink it.
هيا، اشربيه
They left, don't drink it.
غادروا، لا تشربه
You had a hard time.
مررت بوقت عصيب
Don't drink it next time.
لا تشربه المرة القادمة
Darling.
دارلينغ
As long as she doesn't go to the hospital,
طالما أنها لا تذهب إلى المستشفى
we have to drink it every day.
يجب أن نشربه كل يوم
Don't you find it strange?
ألا تجدين ذلك غريبًا؟
She's a cancer patient,
إنها مريضة بسرطان
yet she looks so healthy every day.
لكنها تبدو بصحة جيدة جدًا كل يوم
When we tried to take her to the hospital,
عندما حاولنا نقلها إلى المستشفى
she could still struggle free from your grasp.
كان يمكنها أن تكافح بعيدا عن متناول يدك
Is that reasonable?
هل هذا معقول؟
How's everything at Chen Guihua's side?
كيف كل شيء إلى جانب تشن
Preparing for pregnancy?
للاستعداد للحمل؟
We need to start taking action.
علينا البدء في اتخاذ إجراء
(Compound Vitamin B Tablets)
(قسائم فيتامين باء)
Who's there?
من هناك؟
Chun, Mom, it's me.
تشون يا أمي هذا أنا
Jing, it's so early.
جينغ، الوقت مبكر جدًا
What's going on?
ماذا يجري؟
Mom.
أمي
Look.
انظر
This medicine you're taking is fake.
هذا الدواء الذي تأخذه مزيف
Were you deceived by the doctor in the hometown?
هل خدعك الطبيب في مسقط رأسك؟
Yes.
نعم
I was fooled.
لقد خُدعت
This quack...
هذا الدجال...
Look.
انظر
Luckily, I found out early.
لحسن الحظ اكتشفت مبكرا
Here, Mom.
هيا يا أمي
From now on, take this.
من الآن فصاعدًا خذي هذا
What's this?
ما هذا؟
This is imported medicine I bought through a friend.
هذا دواء مستورد اشتريته عن طريق صديق
Not only does it
هذا لا يمنع فقط
prevent the spread of cancer cells,
منع انتشار خلايا السرطان
but it also has a therapeutic effect if taken long-term.
ولكن له أيضا تأثير علاجي إذا أخذ على المدى الطويل
Imported?
مستوردة؟
It must be expensive.
لا بد أنها باهظة الثمن
Don't care about the price.
لا يهمني الثمن
Don't worry.
لا تقلق
Just focus on taking care of your health.
ركزي على الاعتناء بصحتك فحسب
Thanks, Jing.
شكرًا جينغ
It's nothing, Mom.
لا شيء يا أمي
I'm telling you, Yu Jing,
أنا أقول لك، يو جينغ
I'm the man in this family.
أنا الرجل في هذه العائلة
Whether to sell the house or the car is my decision.
إمّا بيع المنزل أو السيارة هو قراري
You're a man,
أنت رجل
but most of the money in this family is earned by me.
لكن معظم المال في هذه العائلة يكسبه لي
When I say sell the house, we sell it.
عندما أقول إننا نبيع المنزل
That's not right.
هذا ليس صحيحًا
Back then, Jiahui supported you in starting your business.
في ذلك الوقت، قدم لك جياهوي الدعم في بدء عملك
He sold the house and the car.
بيع المنزل والسيارة
Mom.
أمي
Why are you arguing with me?
لماذا تتذرع بي؟
Who was it all for?
لماذا فعلت كل شيء؟
Wasn't it for you?
ألم يكن هذا لك؟
For me?
من أجلي؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تعني؟
To buy the medicine worth tens of thousands yuan for you,
لشراء الدواء قيمته عشرات الآلاف من يوان لك
we had to mortgage the car and the house.
كان علينا رهن السيارة والمنزل
Was it the medicine Jing said this morning?
هل كان الدواء الذي قاله جينغ هذا الصباح
Tens of thousands?
عشرات الآلاف؟
Yes.
نعم
No, I don't need it.
لا، لا أحتاج إليها
I...
أنا...
My illness doesn't matter.
مرضي لا يهم
Save it for my grandchild.
أنقذه من أجل حفيدي
That's right, Jing.
هذا صحيح أيها جينغ
Once you mortgage the house, where can you stay?
بمجرد أن ترهن المنزل أين يمكنك البقاء؟
As long as you're healthy,
ما دامت بصحة جيدة
I don't need to hurry to prepare for pregnancy.
لا حاجة لأن أسرع للاستعداد للحمل
I can earn money together with Jiahui
يمكنني كسب المال مع جياهوي
in the future.
في المستقبل
The contracts only need the signatures of both parties to take effect.
العقود لا تحتاج إلا إلى توقيعات الطرفين لبدء النفاذ
Come on, sign it.
هيا، وقع عليه
I still feel something's not right.
ما زلت أشعر بأن شيئًا ليس صحيحًا
Let's think about it again.
لنفكر في الأمر مرة أخرى
Gu Jiahui.
غو جياهوي
Are you a man?
هل أنت رجل؟
Is money or a person's life more important?
هل المال أم حياة الشخص أكثر أهمية؟
This is your mother!
هذه أمك!
You're right.
أنت على حق
This is my mother.
هذه أمي
Even if we have to sell everything, we must cure her illness.
حتى لو كان علينا بيع كل شيء، يجب أن نعالج مرضها
I'll sign.
يمكنني التوقيع
No!
لا
It's fake.
إنها مزيفة
Yu Chun, tell them.
يو تشون، قل لهم
Aunt's cancer is fake.
سرطان العمة مزيف
The medical report was edited by someone online.
قام أحدهم بتحرير التقرير الطبي عبر الإنترنت
So, don't sell the house or the car.
لذا لا تبيع المنزل أو السيارة
Fine.
حسنا
I genuinely cared for you,
أنا أهتم لأمرك بصدق
but what I got in return was your lies, right?
لكن ما وصلت إليه هو أكاذيبك، صحيح؟
I really feel sad for myself.
أشعر بالحزن على نفسي حقًا
It's all because you didn't have a kid in three years.
هذا كله لأنك لم يكن لديك طفل منذ ثلاث سنوات
What can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل
Mom.
أمي
I'm not good with sweet talk.
أنا لا أجيد التحدث حلو
I rarely
نادرا ما أخدمك
serve you and take care of you well,
أن تخدمك وتعتني بك جيدًا
but I give you money every year.
لكنني أعطيك المال كل عام
I express my filial piety in my own way.
أعبر عن تقوى البنوة بطريقي
However,
لكن
by doing this,
وبذلك
you've really hurt me.
لقد آذيتني حقا
Jing.
جينغ
There's no need to say anything else, Mom.
لا داعي لقول شيء آخر يا أمي
I want to be alone and calm down.
أريد أن أكون وحدي وأهدأ
Jing.
جينغ
Since it's fake,
بما أنها مزيفة
let's return the medicine.
دعونا نعود الدواء
The medicine?
الدواء؟
It was bought online for less than a hundred.
اشتريت على الإنترنت لأقل من مائة
That's calcium tablets.
إنها أقراص الكالسيوم
Gu Jiahui.
غو جياهوي
Look at this.
انظر إلى هذا
She's not sick after all.
إنها ليست مريضة في النهاية
Wait.
مهلًا
That's too much.
هذا مبالغ فيه
She's pretending to be sick.
إنها تتظاهر بأنها مريضة
From now on, cooperate with me.
من الآن فصاعدًا، تعاونت معي
This is
هذا يتعلق
beating her
ضربها
at her own game.
في لعبتها
It smells great.
رائحته رائعة
Aunt, are you planning something big?
عمّتي، هل تخطط لشيء كبير؟
I must let her know
يجب أن أخبرها
that Chen Guihua isn't easy to deal with.
أن تشن غويهوا ليس من السهل التعامل معه